好的  等我妈进来  我们该做什么呢
Okay, when my mom comes in, what are we going to do?
降低她的期望值
Lower her expectations.
正是
Exactly.
准备好体验一下帕克的方法发威吧
Get ready to experience the Parker way in action.
- 你好啊  鲁尼女士  - 哦
- Hey, Mrs. Rooney. - Oh.
你知道你现在有很多活要干
I know you have a lot to do around here.
我帮你把洗碗机里的碟子都拿出来了
So I unloaded the dishwasher for you.
谢谢你了  埃文
Well, thank you, Evan.
哦  那些碟子还都是脏的呢
Oh, but those dishes were dirty.
只不过有一点脏罢了
They seemed a little crusty.
不过我才不介意您怎么操持家务呢
But I'm not here to judge how you keep house, ma'am.
抱歉了  鲁尼女士
Sorry, Mrs. Rooney.
让我来帮您吧
Let me help you.
抱歉
Oops.
拜托  埃文
Come on, Evan.
以后做事请小心一点啊
Be a little more careful.
哎呀
Oops.
看来我被埃文带的也笨手笨脚的了
Looks like I caught the clumsies from Evan.
孩子们  停手吧
Boys, please stop.
我很抱歉  鲁尼女士
I feel terrible, Mrs. Rooney.
我去拿把拖把把这里收拾了吧
Let me get the broom and help clean up.
别别别  别帮我
No no no. Do not help.
这事还是我自己来比较好
I will take care of this myself.
谁的方法
What's the way?
帕克的方法
The Parker way.